＜（宇佐）中学の俺は
災難続きだった＞
Middle school was a disaster for me.
＜あの３年間は忘れて＞
I want to forget those three years ever happened,
＜高校生活は　心地よく＞
and spend high school in peace and quiet.
＜穏やかに過ごしたい…＞
＜そして　知的で＞
With a decent, intelligent girlfriend.
＜清楚な彼女と…＞
＜そう…＞
Yes.
＜例えば…＞
Just imagine
＜あんな彼女と　青春の日々を…＞
if I could spend my youth with a girl like her.
For Instance
Episode One
≪（田神）宇佐
Usa.
宇佐！
Usa!
Tagami.
田神
（田神）図書委員の仕事なんか
Let's finish library duty so we can go home.
さっさと終わらせて帰ろうぜ
そーいや　今日からだっけ？
一人暮らし
Oh, yeah.
You're living on your own as of today, right?
Yep.
You're so lucky.
いいよな～　俺んちの親も
転勤になんねえかなあ
I wish my parents had to move because of work, too.
アパート　どんなの？
How's your new place?
Actually, I haven't visited the complex yet.
それが　今日　初めて行くんだよね
管理人さんには会ったけど
I've met the manager before, though.
What?
≪（田神）はあ　何それ？
Seriously?
There was an issue with the previous tenant's belongings...
前の人の荷物が　どうたらで
Oh, she left.
あッ　帰っちゃった
＜贅沢は言わない＞
I'm not asking for much.
＜自由な新生活のためならば＞
I just want a new life where I can be free.
あそこを右
Turn right up ahead.
＜古い家が多いな＞
There are so many old buildings.
It's very quiet and peaceful.
＜のどかで　落ち着いてて＞
Oh, there's a grade school.
＜おッ　小学校＞
＜変なヤツもいなさそうだ＞
Doesn't seem like there are many weirdos around.
W...
Weirdo found.
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
＜警察に電話…＞
W...
We
Weirdo
Found
We
Weirdo
Found
Gotta call the cops...
＜ヤベ　気づかれた！＞
Crap, he saw me!
（シロ）あれ　宇佐君！
Huh? Usa-kun?
小学校　好きなの？
Do you like grade schools?
誰が！　というか何で俺の名前！？
Hell no!
And how do you know my name?!
≪（警官）ちょっと君達
Excuse me, gentlemen.
小学校を
のぞいてる変な男がいるって
We had a report of a strange man
lurking around, peeping into the grade school.
通報があったんだけど
えッ？
アンタだ　アンタ
You! He means you!
Don't look at me
≪（シロ）えッ
のぞいたりしてないよ
What? I wasn't peeping.
金網の中に頭
突っ込んでたじゃないっすか
You were poking your head through the hole in the fence!
But when you see a hole like this, you have to poke in.
こんな穴　見つけちゃったら
突っ込まざるをえないでしょ
Indeed.
確かに　少年心も男心も
くすぐられる状況ではあるが…
This is an enticing situation for both boys and men...
Are you listening to yourself, Officer?
何言ってんの　おまわりさん
It's similar to wanting to coast on a shopping cart
スーパーのカートで
シャーッとやりたいとか
or spin around in a chair with your hands in the air.
イスの上で両手両足伸ばして
クルクルしたいとか
そういった幾多の誘惑に
みんな耐え忍んで
All of us must resist many temptations such as these
every day of our lives.
生きてるんじゃないかな？
No, I don't have that problem...
いえ　僕は別に…
しかし　子供の安全に
敏感な世の中だ
However, the safety of our children is a sensitive topic in our society.
そういうことは…
You better not be...
No, no! My mind is indeed full of dirty thoughts,
いやいや　頭はエロでいっぱいですが
but I'm too focused on high school girls who have just turned eighteen,
１８歳になりたて女子高生以上の
女子がみっちりで
so I have no room in my mind for grade schoolers!
小学生が入る
スキなんてないですよ！
人並みの倫理観はあるようだが…
It appears that you have some degree of morals.
He does not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
He
does
not!
I'm more into train station stairways.
≪（シロ）どうせなら
駅前の階段に行きます→
そんで　全然　見てないのに
I like to stand there, not looking at a thing,
「何見てんだよ　おっさん」と
while the girls glare at me like, "What are you looking at, you creep?"
さげすんだ目で
理不尽に　にらまれたい
Grab
Something's definitely wrong with you.
やっぱり　あなた変ですね
I need you to come down to the station with me.
ちょっと派出所まで来てください
えッ？
This is my chance.
＜今のうちに…＞
≪（警官）さっさと来なさい！
Come on, get moving.
≪（シロ）あッ　宇佐君！
Oh, Usa-kun!
Wait!
待って～！
Kawai
Complex
（住子）どうしたの？
顔色悪いわよ
What's the matter?
You're as white as a ghost.
いえ　ちょっと変な人がいて…
I ran into a weirdo on the way here...
まあ　物騒ね
早く家に　お上がりなさいな
My, how frightening.
Come inside, quickly.
But really, how did he know my name?
＜しかし　何で
あの人　俺の名前を…＞
＜いかんいかん
ケチがつくから　もう忘れよう＞
I've gotta stop that.
I'm just making things worse. Forget it!
管理人さん
≪（住子）住子さんて呼んでね
Ma'am...
You can call me Sumiko-san.
住子さん
今日からよろしくお願いします
Sumiko-san, I'm looking forward to living here.
こちらこそ　想像してたより
古くて驚いたでしょ？
We're glad to have you.
I'm sure you weren't expecting it to be such an old building.
いや　何かいい感じです
うふふ
Actually, i think it's nice.
ありがとう
まずは　お茶でも飲む？
Thank you.
Would you like some tea? Or do you want to see your room first?
お部屋　見る？
あ　部屋　見たいっす
Oh, I want to see my room!
It's huge!
広ッ！　あれ　四畳半じゃ？
Er, I thought it was four and a half tatami mats...
ああ　それはね…
Oh, about that...
こうして　こうで　四畳半
If you go like this,
it's four and a half mats.
あの　それって…
Are you telling me...
Pat
That wasn't nice, Usa-kun.
ヒドいな～　宇佐君
ギャーッ！
何で　ここに！？
住人だもの
Why are you here?!
I live here.
How do you know my name?!
何で俺の名前！？
Sumiko-san told me. She also showed me a picture.
住子さんから聞いたし　写真も
Don't tell me that he's my roommate!
ルームメイトって
まさか　この人と！？
仕切っただけの部屋に！
W-With only a divider between us?!
I'll admit that the wall is a little thin.
確かに壁は薄いわね
No, that might as well be a curtain!
いや　そいつカーテンの仲間ですから
I refuse to live with this person!
嫌ですよ　こんな人と！
≪（住子）そんな
よく知らないでしょ
Now, now. You barely know him.
Yeah, but...
そりゃあ…
大丈夫よ
You don't need to worry.
シロ君は変態だけど
基本　無害で
Shiro-kun's a pervert, but he's quite harmless.
むしろ害を
与えられたいタイプだから
In fact, he prefers to be on the receiving end of any harm.
ヘタレでＭでチキンカツの
好きなチキンカス
He's a good-for-nothing masochist and a spineless chicken who likes chicken cutlets.
よく知った方が
ヒドいじゃないっすか！
Knowing more about him is even worse!
I love how Sumiko-san can sound so polite when she's insulting me.
住子さんの言葉は控えめなようで
しんらつなのが　いいなあ
＜ダメだ　ここで流されちゃ＞
No! I can't go with the flow,
or it'll be middle school all over again!
＜中学の二の舞だ＞
とにかく親に確認して
Anyway, I need to talk to my parents first.
今日は　友達んちに泊まります！
I'll be staying at a friend's place today.
えッ　待って
Wait.
＜俺は　穏やかな
暮らしがしたいんだ＞
I want to live in peace and quiet.
＜そして　知的で清楚な…＞
With a decent, intelligent...
＜例えば＞
Just imagine
＜こんな彼女と＞
if I could spend my youth
＜青春の日々を…＞
with a girl like her.
ああ　律ちゃん
おかえりなさい
Hey, Rit-chan.
Welcome home.
Did I just trigger a flag?
＜これはフラグか…＞
＜それともワナか＞
Or is this a trap?
Rit-chan.
律ちゃん　前にも話したけど
This is Usa-kun, the new resident I told you about.
今日から住人になる宇佐君
よ　よろしくお願いします
P-Pleased to meet you!
Likewise.
こちらこそ　俺は城崎
シロって呼んで
I'm Shirosaki. You can call me Shiro.
The way you would call a dog.
できるだけ犬っぽく
I'm not really pleased to meet you.
あなたは別に
よろしくしたくないです
（律）河合律です
I'm Kawai Ritsu.
She's a second year at North High.
北高の２年生なの
宇佐君も北高よね？
You're also a North High student, yes?
あッ　はい
Oh, yes!
I don't believe it!
＜信じらんねえ　超好みの女子と
同じアパートなんて＞
I'm living in the same building as a girl who's totally my type!
あの　さっき
図書室で会いましたよね？
Uh, I believe we met at the library earlier.
Met?
あ　いや　一方的に見ただけっす
Er, I guess it was just me looking at you...
I thought our eyes met...
＜目が合ったと思ったのに…＞
Uh, what a coincidence that we go to the same high school, huh?
あの　同じ高校って偶然ですね
俺　１年なんですけど
まだ慣れてなくて
I'm a first year, so I don't know my way around yet.
この辺のこと　よく知らないんで
This area is also new to me,
so if you could show me aro—
色々　教えてくださ…
Girls' area.
女子エリア
Right!
はい？
I didn't tell you yet, did I?
まだ　話してなかったわね→
This building has areas restricted to girls-only and boys-only.
うちは男女で
行動範囲を制限してるの
C
M
F
Men not allowed
あの　これって
制限されてるの男だけですよね
Men not allowed
Uh, I think it's only the boys who are restricted here...
The restrooms and bathrooms are also separate, so be careful.
Women
Men
トイレとお風呂
男女別々だから気をつけてね
You've built quite a class society in this little complex.
同じ住居で
とんだ格差社会ですね
It's important for young people to learn about class from an early age!
若者が格差を学ぶのは大事よ
下から底辺まで
From the bottom to the very bottom.
下ばっかり　喜んで！
Lower and lower! Count me in!
下から学ぶって
ワードからして　何か
Doesn't "learning from the bottom" sound dirty?
ヒワイ　ドッキドッキ…
My heart is racing...
You need to shut your mouth right now!
女の子いるのに
こんな人　危ないんじゃ…
Is it really safe to let this person live around women?
It's fine.
≪（住子）大丈夫よ　要所要所に
グッズが置いてあるから
We've left various items lying around.
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
女子エリア　超おっかない
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
The girls' area looks absolutely terrifying.
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bamboo Sword
+100 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Bat (Metal)
+160 Attack
Stun Gun
+260 Attack
Wooden Sword
+150 Attack
Pepper Spray
+190 Attack
Spiked Bat
+230 Attack
Naginata
+200 Attack
でも　よかった
現実　受け入れてくれたみたいで
I'm glad, though.
It looks like you've accepted reality.
えッ？
よろしくルームメイト
Good to have you, roommate.
お互い干渉せず
時々　物理的に縛ってくれ
We don't have to tie each other down, as long as you tie me up now and then.
すいません　無理です　この現実
Yeah, sorry. I can't accept that reality.
さっきまでノリノリだったのに
You seemed pretty excited a moment ago.
ねえ
No kidding.
Th-That was because...
そ　それは　とにかく保留です！
Anyway! I'm withholding judgment!
[TEL]（母）いまさら何言ってんのよ
Why are you complaining now?
[TEL]一人暮らしできるなら
どんな部屋でも文句言わない
You promised that you'd be happy with any place as long as you got to live alone.
[TEL]て　約束したでしょ
[TEL]同室の人も
個性的で面白いって聞いたわ
And I heard that your roommate is a fun and unique person.
アレを個性で流さないでくれる？
"Unique" isn't the word to describe him.
つーか　他人が同室な時点で
一人暮らしじゃねーじゃん
And I'm not living alone if I have a roommate!
[TEL]アンタはホント
細かいこと気にするわね
You're so fussy about the little details.
母さんが粗いんだよ　その
いい加減な性格のせいで
No, you're just too lax!
Do you realize how difficult it's been for me because of your—
俺が　どんなに苦労し…
[TEL]ああ　もううるさいわね！
Stop whining already.
[TEL]特別に
安くしてもらってるんだから
We're getting a great deal, so don't ask for the moon.
[TEL]贅沢言わないの　しかも平日は
The manager even cooks meals for you on weekdays.
[TEL]管理人さんが
ご飯まで作ってくれるのよ
Do you know how to cook?
[TEL]これ以上　言うと
仕送りしないからね
If you keep this up, I'll stop sending money.
Honestly, ever since you were little, you always—
＜まあ確かに　一人暮らししたくて＞
Well, it's true
that I pushed them to let me live alone.
＜無理通したのは俺だし…＞
＜建物古いけど　雰囲気は好きだし＞
The building is pretty old, but I like the atmosphere.
Plus...
＜それに…＞
I wonder which room is hers...
＜どの部屋なんだろう？＞
I'm borrowing slippers.
ジョリ借りま～す
＜窓から顔出さないかな＞
Maybe she'll look out the window?
≪（住子）宇佐君
Usa-kun.
ののの　のぞこうなんて
思ってないっすよ
I-I wasn't trying to peep or anything!
顔出してくれないか　あわよくば
生着替えとかなんて　全然！
I wasn't hoping to catch a glimpse of her
looking outside or changing or anything!
お　思ってません！
思ってるだけならいいわよ→
As long as you don't act on that thought.
I swear the thought never crossed my mind!
お茶いれたの
つきあってくれない？
I made tea.
Would you care to join me?
ご飯は　ここで食べるのよ
This is where we eat our meals.
律ちゃんも一緒にね
Rit-chan also eats here.
そ　そうすか
R-Really...
律ちゃんは手強いわよ
It won't be easy to win over Rit-chan.
Oh, dear. Are you all right?
あらあら　大丈夫？
I'm sorry! I've always wanted to try that!
ごめんなさい
一度やってみたかったの
You know, like those side characters in romance dramas
恋愛ドラマで助言でも何でもない
意味深なだけのセリフを
who say mysterious things that have no real meaning!
したり顔で吐く女脇役！
へえ…　名演技っすね
You're a pretty good actress.
≪（住子）律ちゃんは
私の兄の孫なの→
Rit-chan is my older brother's granddaughter.
ちょっとマイペースだけど
いい子だから
She does things at her own pace, but she's a good girl, so get to know her.
仲良くしてあげてね
もちろん
Of course.
Oh, wait. That wasn't what I meant to say.
違うわ　こうじゃなくて…
Heh
仲良くしようとせずに
仲良くなって
Get to know her without really getting to know her.
Heh
それも女脇役的セリフですか？
Was that a side character line, as well?
Heh
Men's Washroom
＜仲良くなんて…
メッチャなりてーよ＞
I'm dying to get to know her.
＜本　好きなんだな＞
She must like to read.
＜もう少しで共同エリア＞
She's about to reach the common area.
＜あれ？＞
Huh?
＜何　アレ？＞
What's she doing?
Stare
The Right
Way to
Repent
＜本　近い　近い＞
She's holding the book too close.
＜髪　サラサラ＞
Look at her hair flutter...
＜ああ　何て
癒やされる　ひととき…＞
Oh, this is pure bliss to behold...
Usa-kun!
宇佐く～ん！
荷物に布団ないけど
You didn't bring a futon. Where are you gonna sleep?
夜どーすんの？
Hey! You're too loud!
My parents don't care about anything, so I'll go without one!
But the nights are still cold.
It doesn't matter! Just go away!
I know. We can sleep in a 111 shape.
No way!
And what's supposed to be in the middle?!
We can try a B shape, then.
Damn, I pictured that for a second!
じゃあ　４８の字
How about a 48 shape, then?
Where'd you get that impossible number from?!
何　その極めそうな数字
If you're gonna do that, a 69 would be easier—
無理なく寝るなら６９とか…
ああ　俺のバカ
I'm an idiot!
ち　違うんです
今のは言葉のアヤで…
I-It's not what you think!
That was just a figure of speech!
Usa-kun! You're in
宇佐君　そこ女子エリア
the girls' area.
あの…　の…
Uh... No...
My dream was to live in peace and quiet.
Hey, Usa-kun. Are you cold?
≪（シロ）ねえ　宇佐君
寒くない？
≪（シロ）ねえ　宇佐君→
Hey, Usa-kun.
律ちゃんのケツ竹刀って
絶妙な痛さじゃない？
Rit-chan can really make your ass sting with that wooden sword, huh?
You seriously need to stop talking!
アンタ　ホント
黙っててくださいよ！
＜もう　諦めました＞
I've given up on that dream.
どうやって潜り込んだんだか
How'd you sneak inside?
まあ　いいや　出て来いよ
そこにいるのは分かってんだ
Whatever, just show yourself.
I know you're there.
Let's play.
遊ぼうぜ
お断りします
I refuse.
Oh, yeah! You're here!
あッ　いるんだった
ささやかな妄想遊びが
I can't play make-believe anymore!
I didn't realize that a roommate might ruin my games.
ルームメイトに　こんな弊害が…
But come to think of it,
this sense of shame is amazing
いたたまれない
俺の方が害　受けてますよ
But come to think of it,
this sense of shame is amazing
I'm the one who's had everything ruined so badly that I want to leave.
But come to think of it,
this sense of shame is amazing
宇佐君も妄想劇ぐらいするだろ！
しません！
Surely you act out your fantasies too, don't you?
Never.
「ここは俺に任せて先に行け！」
とか
You don't say stuff like, "Go on! I'll take care of this"?
Never.
しません！
キレイな　お姉さんに
You don't imagine pretty ladies saying,
"You don't have any experience? Want me to show you how it's done?"
「経験ないの　教えてあげようか」
とか
Th-That's cheating.
そ　それはズルい…
しっかし宇佐君　順応早いね
But seriously, you've adapted fairly quickly.
３日もたてば慣れますよ
Three days is long enough to get used to anything.
そう？　住人みんなと
すぐ仲良くなれそうだね
Really?
You'll probably be on good terms with all of the residents in no time.
住子さんはともかく
河合先輩は無理だと思います
That might be true for Sumiko-san,
but I don't see how that'll happen with Kawai-senpai.
何で？
Why not?
Dinner
ケツ竹刀されてから
目も合わせないし
Dinner
She hasn't looked at me since she whacked my ass with the bamboo sword.
学校でも無視だし…
Senpai!
She always ignores me at school.
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
Though that's partly
because she's
always reading
ニコリともしないし
And she never smiles.
無表情　無関心すぎませんか？
あの人
Isn't she taking the apathetic, stony-face thing a little too far?
え～　そうかな？
そんな印象なかったけど
You think so?
I've never gotten that impression.
Didn't you love her expression when she was whacking your ass?
ケツ竹刀のときの顔とか
最高じゃない！
No
麻弓さんや彩花ちゃんと
話してるときもさ
No
Same when she's talking to Mayumi-san and Sayaka-chan.
Who are they?
誰っすか？
２人とも旅行中だから
Oh, you haven't met them because they're both traveling right now.
会ってないっけ？
ＯＬの麻弓さんと
Mayumi-san's an office lady and Sayaka-chan's a college student.
女子大生の彩花ちゃん
麻弓さんは写真があるよ
I have a picture of Mayumi-san.
いい感じのお姉さんだよ
She's a very pretty lady.
妄想かなったりして
Maybe your fantasy will become reality.
Shiro-kun, can you go buy some fish for me?
シロ君　お魚買ってきてくれない？
More domineering, please!
もっと　傲慢にお願いします
≪（住子）あら　ごめんなさい
魚買って来いよ　この豚野郎！
Oh, forgive me.
Go buy some fish, you vulgar pig.
御意！
＜でも＞
As you wish!
But I only have his word to go on.
＜この人の言うことだしなあ＞
＜妄想なら　１つかなってる＞
At least one fantasy has been realized.
＜一人暮らし先に　好みの女の子＞
I'm living in the same building as a girl who's my type.
＜でも　現実は…＞
But reality
Thank you. Come again.
≪（コンビニ店員）
ありがとうございました
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
＜しょっぱい…＞
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
is not as sweet.
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
A bitter pill
Though I'm not into
blunt girls like her, anyway
It's getting dark.
＜もう　暗くなるのに＞
＜女一人で　こんなとこ…＞
What's a girl doing out here alone?
＜乳　スゲー！＞
Big tits!
＜酒の量も　スゲー！＞
And a big drinker...
＜俺には手に
負えなさそうなタイプだな＞
Doesn't look like a girl I could handle.
＜まだ飲むんかい＞
She hasn't had enough?
＜わっかりやすく失恋してるな～＞
It's so obvious that she just had her heart broken...
（麻弓）健二のバカヤロー！
最低男！
Kenji, you idiot!
You total sleaze bag!
I didn't know people actually did this in real life.
＜こういうのホントに
やる人いるんだ…＞
お前が結婚するときは
友人装って
When you get married, I'll pretend to be a friend and send,
「２人でよくラブドール作ってる
会社の株を買いましたね」
"Remember how we used to buy shares in that company that makes sex dolls?
I bet you chose a wife who's real good at reading the air! (lol)
「そんな健二さんが選んだ人は」
「空気読める嫁でしょうね（笑）」
「男は結婚で一皮むける
といいますが」
They say men break out of their shell after getting married,
「数年前に
手術でむいたばかりなので」
but you just had surgery to break out of yours a few years ago, so be careful."
「気をつけて」って
電報打ってやる！
to everyone attending!
I pity Kenji.
＜ほっとこう…＞
I should let her be.
あの！　そんなとこいると
危ないですよ
Excuse me! It's not safe to stand there!
足フラフラだし
You can barely stand up straight.
＜あれ　この人どっかで…＞
Wait, I've seen her before...
ガキにナンパされるほど
困ってないから
I'm not so desperate that I need a kid to hit on me.
違いますよ　俺は単に
注意しただけで
I'm not hitting on you!
I was just telling you to be careful.
そんな気　全く…
I'm not interested.
I can't even get a kid who's totally
こんな童貞くさいヤツにさえ
見向きもされない私って…
a virgin to look twice at me...
＜うわッ　この人…＞
God, she's...
a total pain
and incredibly rude!
川で適度に溺れて
罪の意識植え付けてやる！
I'll drown myself in the river to make you feel guilty!
うあ～　そんな気あった！
ありました
Okay, okay! I was interested! I'm interested!
僕ってば　うっかり！
It was a slip of the tongue!
You're an extremely attractive person,
お姉さんは非常に魅力的ですが
僕には荷が重いというか…
but I don't think I could meet your needs...
重いって言うな～！
Don't call me needy!
＜ああ　もう…＞
Oh, come on...
Damn it!
くそッ
ちょっと下半身新品だからって
Don't get all cocky because your privates are still unused.
調子に乗んなよ！
乗れねえよ！
I'm not being cocky!
てか勝手に認定しないでください
違いますから！
And don't assume that they're unused!
They're not!
A lie
あのさ　コンニャクは食い物だぞ
片栗粉も
Konnyaku is meant to be eaten, you know.
So is starch.
She has no shame.
腹減ったな…
I'm hungry now.
And she's totally random.
Oyakodon... I want oyakodon...
親子丼　親子丼　食べたい…
ゴボウが入った…
ちょっとトランク忘れてますよ！
Hey! You forgot your suitcase!
With burdock...
親子丼…　住子さんの…
I want some of Sumiko-san's oyakodon...
＜うん？
今　住子さんって言った？＞
Did she just say Sumiko-san?
Okay, here you go. Keep hold of it.
はい　これ　ちゃんと持って
ゴミは捨てときますから
I'll throw away the trash for you. Be careful now.
気をつけて
お前…
Hey...
いいヤツだな
You're a nice guy.
I feel like this isn't the first time we've met.
何か　初めて会った気がしないし
＜うわッ＞
Say, why don't I teach you a thing or two?
ねえ　お姉さんが
色々教えてやろ～か？
何してんですか　こんなとこで
What are you doing, and in a place like this?
＜河合先輩！？＞
Kawai-senpai?!
Ow...
何だよ　律ちゃん
What was that for, Rit-chan?
＜ええッ！？＞
I was about to be like, "Thought you were about to live your fantasy? Punk'd!"
…のハズだったのに
お酒くさッ　また酔ってますね
You reek of alcohol.
Are you drunk again?
これじゃまるで
私が襲ってるみたいじゃん
You're making it sound like I was throwing myself at him.
みたいじゃなくて
襲ってたでしょ
It doesn't sound like it. You were.
あの人　酔っぱらうと色々ヒドいから
近づかない方がいいよ
She's a total mess when she's drunk,
so you should stay away.
手遅れな情報
ありがとうございます
Thank you for the oh-so-timely warning.
ところで　あの人って　まさか…
And don't tell me that she...
Hey!
これメッチャ楽しそーじゃね？
This looks like a lot of fun!
＜何してんの　あの人！？＞
What is she doing?!
１番　錦野麻弓
Leading off is Nishikino Mayumi!
おまたが　こすれて熱くなっても
頑張ります！
I'll still keep going even if I get all hot and bothered sliding down!
She really has no shame.
＜どこまで最低なんだ　あの人＞
＜つか　あんなベロベロで
着地で吹っ飛ばされるんじゃ…＞
And she's totally wasted,
so won't she just crash on landing?
Okay! Here I go!
いっくぜ～！
先輩…
Senpai?!
あッ　何か怖いからやめる
Oh, this is kind of scary, so I won't.
あれ？　ただでさえつらいのに
Wait, I'm already in enough pain,
何で　こんな怖いことやるハメに？
so why should I have to do scary things?
意味分かんねえ…
I don't get it.
うわッ　ちょっと　何…
Hey!
What is it?!
うわッ
危ない！
Look out!
Mayumi-chan!
麻弓ちゃん！　酔うと色々
見境ないから
You promised not to drink outside
外で飲まないって
約束したわよね！
because you're such a bad drunk!
律ちゃんも気をつけないと→
And Rit-chan, you need to be careful!
宇佐君が　かばってくれたから
よかったものの…
You're lucky that Usa-kun was there to catch you.
ああ　いえ…
No, I just broke their fall...
単に下敷きになっただけで…
湿布　貼っとこか…
Do you want a compress?
That picture was a lie.
＜写真サギ＞
It's Rit-chan's fault for hitting me out of nowhere.
だって律ちゃんが
突然殴ってきて…
I'm sorry. Next time, I'll throw a dictionary at you.
すいません
次からは辞書投げつけます
I'll die!
死ぬわ！
やめなさ～い！
Enough!
彼ができたから落ち着いてたのに
I thought you settled down after finding a boyfriend,
こんなに荒れて　ケンカでもした？
but you're out of control.
Did you get in a fight?
旅行も明日までだったわよね？
I thought you weren't supposed to return from your trip until tomorrow.
Sob
メール見ちゃった…
I read his e-mails...
アイツ　二股かけてた…
He was two-timing me...
あんなヤツだと思わなかった
I didn't think he was like that...
信じてたのに…
麻弓ちゃん…
I trusted him!
Mayumi-chan...
You truly have poor luck when it comes to men.
ホント　男運悪いわね
見る目がないだけだと思う
I think she just has bad taste.
でも　前が三股
その前が四股だから
But your last boyfriend was three-timing you,
and the one before him was four-timing you,
so you're making progress—
進化はしてる…
みんなヒデーッ！
You're all so mean!
慰めろ！
Just console me!
＜この人の言うことは
あてにならない…＞
Anything he says can't be trusted.
≪（住子）ご飯にしましょうね
ちょっと待っててね
Okay, now.
Let's have dinner.
Wait a moment.
う　う　うわ～ん
（一同）いただきます
Let's eat.
＜親子丼…　あれ？＞
Oyakodon.
Wait,
＜魚…＞
what about the fish?
おいしい…
It's good.
Is that so?
そう？
よかった
I'm glad.
傷しみる？　大丈夫？
Does your mouth hurt?
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm okay.
あ　いや　平気です…
ごめん…
Sorry.
He was right.
＜ホントだ全然　無表情じゃないや＞
She's not stony-faced at all.
おわびに　後で
おっぱいパフパフしてやんよ
To make up, I'll let you fondle my boobs.
≪（住子）麻弓ちゃん！
Mayumi-chan!
A
We'll
all
stay
pitiful
tomorrow
shi
ta
mo
bo
ku
ra
wa
mi
n
na
ka
wa
i
so
u
A
Preview
We have a long holiday coming up.
I didn't want to be reminded of that, Usa!
もうすぐ連休っすね
ヤなこと思い出させんな！
Oh? The best way to spend a holiday is to visit popular dating spots
各地のデートスポットに　あえて
１人で出かけて切なくなる
to make yourself sad, right?
な～んて最高の過ごし方だよね
うっさい！
Shut up!
Thank you!
In that case, I'll use this cursed ring that I found
こうなったら　怪しい骨董屋で
手に入れた呪いの指輪で
at a shady antique store to curse every happy couple in the world!
全世界の幸せなカップルを
呪ってやる！
Mayumi-san! The manual says that the wearer will be cursed!
麻弓さん　説明書に　それ
身につけた人が呪われるって
I already put it on.
Let's see... "The wearer will never be loved by the ones they love
つけちゃったよ
何？　指輪をつけた者は
Episode Two
Could It Be
nor loved by the ones they don't love."
思う人には思われず
思わぬ人にも思われず
That means...
それって　つまり…
現状維持？
Nothing's changed?